Preliminary Guide to the Yale School of Drama Production Script Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Yale School of Drama Production Script Collection
1966-2010
DRA 17
Yale University Arts Library
57.96
(127 boxes)
The collection consists of production scripts from the Yale School of Drama, including dramaturgical cut scripts, early scripts, promptbooks, production books, and regular scripts.
Yale School of Drama
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Yale School of Drama Production Scripts Collection was housed in the former Drama Library until its transfer to the Robert B. Haas Family Arts Library in 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of production scripts from the Yale School of Drama, including dramaturgical cut scripts, early scripts, promptbooks, production books, and regular scripts. Individual records for these scripts are also available in Orbis.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: I. Production Scripts. II. Unproduced Scripts.
Arranged chronologically by year of production and then alphabetically by last name of the author or translator within each year.
Drama; Scripts; Yale School of Drama
- Production Scripts, 1966-2010; Series I
  - The Patriarch, 1926 (Box 1)
  - What Color Goes with Brown?, 1966-1967 (Box 103)
  - What Color Goes With Brown? (Part II), 1966-1967 (Box 126 Oversize)
  - Vampire, 1967-1968 (Box 103)
  - You Can't Take it With You, 1968-1969 (Box 103)
  - Workday, 1969-1970 (Box 103)
  - Take Me to Your Paddy Wagon, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Room Nerves, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - After the Party, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Essie Mae, 1970-1971 (Box 103)
  - Tevening hours. (Scene 5 of the Tragedy of practical living), 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Donner, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Donner, 1970-1971 (Box 126 Oversize)
  - Kivuli, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Ivona, Princess of Burgundia, 1971-1972 (Box 127 Oversize)
  - Three Cuckolds, 1971-1972 (Box 104)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1971-1972 (Box 127 Oversize)
  - 1913, 1971-1972 (Box 104)
  - Shearwater, 1972-1973 (Box 105)
  - Marriage of Bette and Boo, 1972-1973 (Box 105)
  - In Good King Charles' Golden Days, 1972-1973 (Box 105)
  - Epiphanies, 1972-1973 (Box 105)
  - The Brothers Karamazov, 1973-1974 (Box 105)
  - Cock-a-doodle Dandy, 1973-1974 (Box 105)
  - Mona Moon, 1973-1974 (Box 105)
  - Wise Men of Helm, 1973-1974 (Box 105)
  - Death Comes to Us All, Mary Agnes, 1974-1975 (Box 106)
  - The Tooth of Crime, 1974-1975 (Box 106)
  - Lulu, 1974-1975 (Box 106)
  - Bartholemew Fair, 1974-1975 (Box 106)
  - Farmyard, 1974-1975 (Box 106)
  - Lady with the Alligator Purse, 1975-1976 (Box 106)
  - Efforts and Study Projects, 1975-1976 (Box 107)
  - Three Sisters, 1975-1976 (Box 107)
  - The Visit, 1975-1976 (Box 107)
  - The Family Reunion, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Attempt at Conversation Between Two People, 1975-1976 (Box 107)
  - Montpelier Paz-zazz, 1975-1976 (Box 107)
  - Uncommon Women and Others, 1975-1976 (Box 107)
  - The Duchess of Malfi, 1975-1976 (Box 108)
  - The Duchess of Malfi, 1975-1976 (Box 127 Oversize)
  - Dottie's Home, 1976-1977 (Box 108)
  - The Sea Gull, 1976-1977 (Box 108)
  - The Government Inspector, 1976-1977 (Box 109)
  - Evenings In, Evenings Out, 1976-1977 (Box 108)
  - A Case of Company, 1976-1977 (Box 109)
  - Henry IV, Parts 1 and 2, 1976-1977 (Box 108)
  - Terra Nova, 1976-1977 (Box 109)
  - The Revenger's Tragedy, 1976-1977 (Box 109)
  - Earth Spirit, 1976-1977 (Box 109)
  - Lion Dancers, 1976-1977 (Box 108)
  - His Master's Voice, 1976-1977 (Box 109)
  - Euripides at Bay, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Alcestis, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - The Last Touch, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - The Complete Works, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Doubt and Resolution, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - A Ride Across Lake Constance, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Heinz: A Comedy in Two Acts, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Divine Primate, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Pas De Deux: A One Act Play in Seven Scenes, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Initiation to the Rite of Suttee, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - The Mad Dog Blues, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Off Season Rates, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - 3 Unnatural Acts, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Phaedra, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Jack, or the Submission, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Interludes, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Yegor Bulychov and the Others, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Returning, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - The Cloud Dream, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Naropa, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - The Pelican, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Twelfth Night, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Drums in the Night, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Body, 1979-1980 (Box 110)
  - Through the Stained Glass, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Jungle of Cities, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - God's Smoke, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - Yerma, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - Family Rites, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Terry by Terry, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Women Beware Women, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Nijinsky, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Hunt's Point, 1980 (Box 110)
  - Loma, 1980 (Box 110)
  - The Bakkhai, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Life is a Dream, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Peer Gynt, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Summerfolk, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - The Learned Ladies, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Tartuffe, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Benten Kozo, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
  - Penelope, 1981 (Box 110)
  - Lydie Breeze, 1981 (Box 110)
  - Spring Awakening, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - As I Lay Dying, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
  - Pillars of Society, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - Baal, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - The Bewitched, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Fanshen, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - The Birthday Party, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - The Confessional, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Phaedra, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - La Ronde, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - House of York, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Macbeth, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - The Tempest, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - The Lower Depths, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Separate Gardens, 1983 (Box 110)
  - He Who Gets Slapped, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - The Vultures, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - The Guiteau Burlesque, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - The Hostage, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Crime on Goat Island, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - The Three Sisters, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Blood Wedding, 1983-1984 (Box 23)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1983-1984 (Box 23)
  - The Terminal Bar, 1983-1984 (Box 110)
  - Pericles, Prince of Tyre, 1983-1984 (Box 23)
  - Alone in the Water, 1983-1984 (Box 110)
  - The Countess Cathleen, 1983-1984 (Box 23)
  - Platonov, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
  - Lorenzaccio, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Help Wanted, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - The Bathhouse, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - The Youngstown Vindicator, 1984-1985 (Box 110)
  - L'aiglon, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
  - Pacific Overtures, 1984-1985 (Box 26)
  - Blue Mass, 1985 (Box 111)
  - A Painted Horse, Drawn (Quartered and Double Exposed), 1985-1986 (Box 111)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, 1985-1986 (Box 26)
  - The Suicide, 1985-1986 (Box 27)
  - The Watertown Primary, 1985-1986 (Box 28)
  - Big Divinity, 1985-1986 (Box 28)
  - A Midsummer's Night Dream, 1985-1986 (Box 29)
  - Translations, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Towering Babble, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Book and Canon, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - True Blue and Trembling, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Measure for Measure, 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - American Beech, 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - The Dragon, 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Electra, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Sea Cruise, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - The Life of Galileo, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Singapore, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Drowning, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - The Sea Gull, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - To Glenda, From Fred, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - The Rendezvous, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Hunger, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Cancer, Leo Rising, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Slippers on the Street, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Santa Bernidisa, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Hamlet, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - The Tempest, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Medea, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - The Resistible Rise of Arturo Ui, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
  - Dead Wall Revery, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - History Man, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - The Swan, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Summerfolk, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Brooklyn After the Glow, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - As You Like It, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - King John, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Pericles, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Titus Andronicus, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Sainte-Carmen of the Main, 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Contradictions of the Heart, 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - The Convert, 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - Three Plays: Drowning / Three Way Stop / The Colorado Catechism, 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - The Tragedy of Hamlet, Prince of California, 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - Fathers and Sons (after Turgenev), 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Cutting In, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Skeletons, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Two Plays: Notes for a Topical Tragedy / One-On-One, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - A Fly, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Dragon Marriage, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Save The Tilt-A-Whirl, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - HamletMachine, 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Seven Plays, 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Mississippi Nude, 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - The Whip-poor-will, 1989-1990 (Box 41)
    Scope and Contents
    On the script the author uses her maiden name, Lisa A. Wing.
  - This City of Dreams, 1990-1991 (Box 41)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1986-1987, 1989-1991, 1990-1991 (Box 41)
  - The Good Person of Szechwan, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
  - Nabo: The Black Man Who Made The Angels Wait, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1988-1991, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
  - The Land Claim, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
  - The Riding Club (South Road Down), 1990-1991 (Box 42)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1988-1991, 1990-1991 (Box 43)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1988-1991, 1990-1991 (Box 43)
  - Dreams are Toys, 1990-1991 (Box 43)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1987-1991, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Hamlet, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - King Richard III, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Twelfth Night, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Streetcar Named Desire, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
  - Blush at Nothing, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    On the script, the author uses her maiden name, Lisa A. Wing.
  - Anthology of Yale Writing, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
  - The Rover, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1989-1992, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
  - Tom's Suite, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
  - The Three Sisters, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
  - The Name of Oedipus, 1991-1992 (Box 47)
  - The Second Coming, 1991-1992 (Box 47)
  - Family Circle, 1991-1992 (Box 47)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing 1989-1992, 1991-1992 (Box 48)
  - Bartleby: The True Story, 1991-1992 (Box 48)
  - If Music, Food, Love…, 1991-1992 (Box 48)
  - Anthology of Yale Writing, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - Snuff Play, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - Amnestia, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - Love in the Underworld, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - Yale Writing 1989-1992, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - The Road, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
  - Measure for Measure, 1991-1992 (Box 50)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1991-1992 (Box 50)
  - Othello, 1991-1992 (Box 50)
  - Stage Door, 1991-1992 (Box 50)
  - Struggle of the Dogs and the Black, 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - Bloody Poetry, 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - The Seagull, 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - Defiling Watercress, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - A Safe Place, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - A Second Coming, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Frankenstein, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Don Juan, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - The Fever, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Macbeth, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - The Tempest, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Titus Andronicus, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - The Merit System, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - Unmerciful Good Fortune, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - Tumbling After, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - The Art of Waiting, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - The Duchess of Malfi, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - Fuente Ovejuna, 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - Peer Gynt, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - The Cherry Orchard, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - The Witching of Drexel Weems, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Love's No Game, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Disappearing Act, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Don Juan's Secret Daughter, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - The Ten Thousand Things, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - The Love of Three Oranges, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Free Ascent, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - Clean, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - Stupid Hunger, Crazy Thirst, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - The History of Henry the Fourth, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - King Lear, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1993-1994 (Box 55)
  - American Passengers, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - The Fattest Man in the World Lives Upstairs, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - The Three Sisters, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - Good Person Of Szechwan, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - A Dog Gets Wise, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - Wild Honey, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - Billy Bishop Goes to War, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Without Your Voice, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Six Fugues, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - The Philanthropist, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Ride Across Lake Constance, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Fences, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - The Adventures of Amy Bock, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Ruffian on the Stair, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Imperceptible Mutabilities in the Third Kingdom, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - All's Well That Ends Well, 1994-1995 (Box 56)
  - Love's Labour's Lost, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Macbeth, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Pericles, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Dreissena Polymorpha, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Orpheus Descending, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - In the Sherman Family Wax Museum, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Teacup For a Shallow Apocalypse, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - Brave Kingdom, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - Diva Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - The Girl Triptych, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - Danton's Death, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - Three Sisters, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - The Art of Success, 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - Wanting a Woman of Valor, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Safe Havens, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Pilgrims of the Night, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Through the Leaves, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Everything Turned Out for the Best…, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Like Rain, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Hors D'oeuvres, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - The Candy Jar, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - Home For Life, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - The Great Highway: Zones of the Spirit, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - Tartuffe, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - The Tempest, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - Henry IV, Part One, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - If Only, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - Forbidden City Blues, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
  - My Life on the Moon, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
  - Persona, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
  - Happy End, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
  - Bloody Poetry, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
  - Cloud 9, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
  - The Pope and the Witch, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - The Plain of Memory, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - Troy Women, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - Gum, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - The Ride Across Lake Constance, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - The Ontological Detective, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - Sitting Man, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - Bulldogs and Firetrucks, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - The Painted Woman, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - Bringing Down DaVinci, 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - The Goat Room, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - Schrödinger's Cat, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - In Arcadia, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - King Lear, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - Post-Coitals, Pre-Nuptials, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - In The Valley of Bowler-Hatted Men, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - This Train Is a Clean Train, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - Christie in Love, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - The Cherry Orchard, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - The Seagull, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - All Things Chicken, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - Black Flamingos, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - The Fatty Arbuckle Spook House Revue, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - Fighting Words, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - A Bright Room Called Day, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - The Birds, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
  - O.B.G.Y.N.T., 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - The Blind, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Revizor Or The Inspector General, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Pains of Youth, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Bagging Groceries, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - God's Acre, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Notorious for Men, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - The Tempest, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Titus Andronicus, 1997-1998 (Box 66)
  - Cymbeline, 1997-1998 (Box 66)
  - King John, 1997-1998 (Box 66)
  - Ava in her Place, 1997-1998 (Box 66)
  - The Road, 1997-1998 (Box 66)
  - Rockaby, Come and Go, Footfalls, 1998-1999 (Box 66)
  - Great Men of Science, 1998-1999 (Box 66)
  - Kind Ness, 1998-1999 (Box 66)
  - They Shoot Beatles, Don't They?, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - Life is a Dream, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - Enter the Night, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - The Danube, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - The Grapes of Wrath, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - Rice Boy, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - Regeneration (Ex?), 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - The Golem, 1998-1999 (Box 67)
  - January 24th, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - Dick in London, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - Cold Water Coming, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - The Collection, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - Campfire Songs for the Apocalypse, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - Is, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - Taming of the Shrew, 1998-1999 (Box 68)
  - Macbeth, 1998-1999 (Box 69)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, 1998-1999 (Box 69)
  - Twelfth Night, 1998-1999 (Box 69)
  - Fit for the Queen, 1998-1999 (Box 69)
  - Cowboy Mouth, 1998-1999 (Box 69)
  - Machinal, 1998-1999 (Box 69)
  - The Waves, 1999-2000 (Box 69)
  - After the Show, 1999-2000 (Box 70)
  - Mad Forest, 1999-2000 (Box 70)
  - The Importance of Being Jesus, 1999-2000 (Box 70)
  - The People vs. The God of Vengeance, 1999-2000 (Box 70)
  - The Prince of Homburg, 1999-2000 (Box 70)
  - One Dead Soldier, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - Down, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - Plays by Mark Novom, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - Farmyard / Ghosttrain, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - Portraits, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - The Birthday Party, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - 1711 Naomi, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
  - Plays produced at Yale School of Drama 1998-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 72)
  - Felling Giants, 1999-2000 (Box 72)
  - All's Well That Ends Well, 1999-2000 (Box 72)
  - As You Like It, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - Hamlet, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - Pericles, Prince of Tyre, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - Tusk, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - Family Stories. Belgrade, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - The Misanthrope, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - Clothes for a Summer Hotel, 1999-2000 (Box 73)
  - The Crazy Locomotive, 1999-2000 (Box 74)
  - King of Litotes, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - The Muckle Man, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - Interlude: A Transformation, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - The Master and Margarita, 2000-2001 (Box 111)
  - God Hates the Irish, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - The Skriker, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - Walls, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - The Lower Depths, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - The Master and Margarita, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - Pearl Blue, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - The Gog/Magog Project, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - Picture 24, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - Body Subjunctive, 2000-2001 (Box 75)
  - Dante's Inferno, 2000-2001 (Box 76)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See DRA 29, Box 1 for Volumes II-IV of Dante's Inferno.
  - Lullabye, 2000-2001 (Box 76)
  - Hamlet, 2000-2001 (Box 76)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 2000-2001 (Box 76)
  - Our Town, 2000-2001 (Box 76)
  - The Sungatherers, 2001-2002 (Box 77)
  - The Mystery Plays, 2001-2002 (Box 77)
  - Pralaya, 2001-2002 (Box 78)
  - The Lady Killers, 2001-2002 (Box 78)
  - like sun fallin in the mouth, 2001-2002 (Box 78)
  - Peer Gynt, 2001-2002 (Box 79)
  - The Trial, 2001-2002 (Box 79)
  - Tennessee Descending, 2001-2002 (Box 79)
  - The Half-Life of Memory, 2001-2002 (Box 80)
  - Cancer Thanksgiving, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Deviant, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Three Sisters, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Macbeth, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Othello, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - The Tempest, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Twelfth Night, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Know Dog, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
  - Rough Magic, 2002-2003 (Box 82)
  - The Great Magician, 2002-2003 (Box 82)
  - Buried History, 2002-2003 (Box 82)
  - … and Jesus moonwalks on the Mississippi, 2002-2003 (Box 82)
  - Alcestis, 2002-2003 (Box 82)
  - The Jammer, 2002-2003 (Box 83)
  - The Special Interest Case of Special Agent Esteban Martinez, 2002-2003 (Box 83)
  - Love – All, 2002-2003 (Box 83)
  - Changes of Heart, 2002-2003 (Box 83)
  - After the Blaze, 2002-2003 (Box 83)
  - Turnpike, 2002-2003 (Box 83)
  - New, 2002-2003 (Box 84)
  - Can You Dig It [As You Like It], 2002-2003 (Box 84)
  - Hamlet, 2002-2003 (Box 84)
  - King Henry IV, Part I, 2002-2003 (Box 84)
  - The Winter's Tale, 2002-2003 (Box 84)
  - Coriolanus, 2002-2003 (Box 84)
  - 3 Children, 2002-2003 (Box 85)
  - Against the Wall, 2002-2003 (Box 85)
  - A Book of Two, 2002-2003 (Box 85)
  - Spring Awakening, 2002-2003 (Box 85)
  - Devil Caught Rope, 2003-2004 (Box 85)
  - A Splash of Nutmeg in Milk, 2003-2004 (Box 86)
  - Dance the Holy Ghost: A Memory Play, 2003-2004 (Box 87)
  - The Summer People, 2003-2004 (Box 87)
  - Last of the Chatterbox Wolves, 2003-2004 (Box 87)
  - Deuce, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
  - …, " said Said, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
  - The Lonesome West, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
  - Ugo's Last Dance, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
  - Banditos, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
  - Uncle Vanya, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - Richard III, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - The Merchant of Venice, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - Romeo & Juliet, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - Saturnalia in Poughkeepsie, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - Empty Sky, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - Orpheus Descending, 2003-2004 (Box 89)
  - The War Is Over, 2004-2005 (Box 89)
  - The Shoemaker's Prodigious Wife, 2004-2005 (Box 89)
  - Willing, 2004-2005 (Box 90)
  - Hedda Gabler, 2004-2005 (Box 90)
  - Bridesburg, 2004-2005 (Box 90)
  - Breakers, 2004-2005 (Box 90)
  - Agency*, 2004-2005 (Box 90)
  - A lone, 2004-2005 (Box 90)
  - The Boy Jumped into the Sea, 2004-2005 (Box 91)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, 2004-2005 (Box 91)
  - Love's Labour's Lost, 2004-2005 (Box 91)
  - As You Like It, 2004-2005 (Box 91)
  - Measure for Measure, 2004-2005 (Box 91)
  - The Life and Death of King John, 2004-2005 (Box 91)
  - Mickey Mouse is Dead., 2004-2005 (Box 92)
  - The Real Thing, 2004-2005 (Box 92)
  - Mirror, Mirror, 2004-2005 (Box 92)
  - Balm in Gilead, 2004-2005 (Box 92)
  - Layla And Majnun, 2005-2006 (Box 92)
  - Attempts on Her Life, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - When It Rains, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - In Times of Disaster, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - After the Flood, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - Hungry, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - In the Red & Brown Water, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - The Brothers Size, 2005-2006 (Box 93)
  - Three Sisters, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - Hamlet, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - Twelfth Night or What You Will, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - Julius Caesar, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - Flicker, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - The Lacy Project, 2005-2006 (Box 94)
  - Ways You Can Survive The World, 2005-2006 (Box 95)
  - The Duchess of Malfi, 2005-2006 (Box 95)
  - Our Town, 2005-2006 (Box 95)
  - Zero Hour, 2006-2007 (Box 95)
  - The Seagull, 2006-2007 (Box 95)
  - Venus, 2006-2007 (Box 95)
  - Tragedy of King Richard III, 2006-2007 (Box 95)
  - Marat/Sade, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - Camino Real, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - Fill Our Mouths, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - Titus Andronicus, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - Speaking Our Mind, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - Edward II, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - Bibles and Candy, 2006-2007 (Box 96)
  - The Wendy Play, 2006-2007 (Box 97)
  - Marcus, Or the Secret of Sweet, 2006-2007 (Box 97)
  - The Imaginary Audience, 2006-2007 (Box 97)
  - Journey to Santiago, 2006-2007 (Box 97)
  - The Emperor of Ice Cream, 2006-2007 (Box 97)
  - Baal, 2007-2008 (Box 97)
  - A Month in the Country, 2007-2008 (Box 97)